Let's suppose we have two signals that really are not that similar.
假设我们有两个不太相似的信号
Dynamic time warping could allow them to match much better than they should.
动态时间规整可以让他们更好地匹配
Look at this example where we use a different shorter signal
观察这个例子 我们使用了不同的短信号
along with the same long one as in the last example.
和前一个例子中相同长度的信号
&gt;&gt; Okay.
— 好
&gt;&gt; While I have to start by matching the 0 and the 3,
— 我们首先匹配 0 和 3
I can match the first half of the x-axis sequence to the 3 so
我把 x 轴序列的前半部分与 3 匹配
that I can get to the negative section of the sequence to get a better match.
然后对序列的负数部分 得到更好的匹配
Then I'm in a positive section of both sequences again.
然后我再次回到两个序列的正数部分
&gt;&gt; Yep, that can be a problem.
— 没错 这里存在一个问题
In this case, the distance is poor because of all those numbers the first
在这个例子中 因为这些数字出现在序列的第一部分
part of the sequence, matching the 3.
与 3 匹配 距离很差
But the severe amount of warping we're allowing
但是经过允许范围内的几次调整
means that the distance is probably smaller than we'd like.
表明距离远远小于我们的期望
&gt;&gt; One way we could force a more reasonable matching is to bound how
— 我们要进行更加合理的匹配
much we're allowed to deviate from the diagonal.
其中一种方式是约束我们偏离直线的距离
&gt;&gt; Yep, we can use Sakoe Chiba Bounds to force more reasonable matches.
— 对 我们可以使用 Sakoe Chiba 约束 进行更加合理的匹配
&gt;&gt; Sakoe Chiba, now you're just making things up.
— Sakoe Chiba 现在你只整理一下
&gt;&gt; No, no, really.
— 不是这样
It says we won't allow matches outside the limits
这表明我们不允许在这些直线
placed by these diagonal lines.
范围以外的匹配
&gt;&gt; That will cause the matches to be worse leading to a bigger distance.
— 这会导致匹配更差 引起更大的距离
&gt;&gt; Which is what we want.
— 这是我们不想要的结果
&gt;&gt; How do we calculate these bounds?
— 我们如何计算这些约束？
&gt;&gt; Often empirically, we set different bounds and
— 经常从经验来说 我们设置不同的约束
use cross validation to make sure they are reasonable.
使用交叉验证确保它们是合理的
&gt;&gt; Well, what if some sections of the signal should have different bounds than
— 如果一部分信号与其他部分
others?
不同怎么办？
&gt;&gt; Like on our example, this section here might have a lot of variance
— 例如在我们例子中 这里的部分可能有许多更短的方差
being shorter along, but the hump may have less variability and shape.
但是隆起部分具有更小的差异性和形状
&gt;&gt; And perhaps the last section can then have more variability again.
— 而且最后一部分再次出现更大的差异性
Basically there are three sections of the signal and
一般来说 这里有三部分的信号
each can have a different amount of allowed warping.
每部分都允许有不同数量的规整
&gt;&gt; We could try to have different Sakoe Chiba Bounds for
— 我们尽量在信号的每部分
each section of the signal.
使用不同的 Sakoe Chiba 约束
&gt;&gt; True, but that seems complicated to train.
— 的确如此 不过训练时看起来非常复杂
And I know you prefer hidden markup models for such problems.
我知道对于这些问题你更喜欢用隐马尔可夫模型
Why don't you introduce them?
为什么不试试呢？
&gt;&gt; Okay, you know they're my favorite technique.
— 好的 你知道这也是我最喜欢的技巧. 最新课程跟课件还有一对一辅导请加wx：udacity6